Tomorrow she'll turn 24 years of age.
明天她就满24岁了
As Zheng Qinwen wraps up a well-earned
郑钦文为自己赢得了一份
early birthday present in Beijing.
来自北京的提前生日礼物
The tussle is over.
这场拉锯战终于结束了
And what a tussle it ended up being.
最终还真是一场苦战
北京时间10月7号晚上
中网1/8决赛
郑钦文在24岁生日前一天
以6比1 2比6 6比4 拿下比赛
郑钦文用正手压向边线
首盘2比1 她又救下3个破发点
连同这一局 首盘最后4局 全归她
Oh, terrific placement.
噢 落点太漂亮了
That forehand just kissing the line.
这一记正手刚好擦着边线
Oh, that's terrific stuff.
噢 打得太棒了
This time it's measured so well, just...
这一次分寸掌握得真好 就
Well, you've seen this before.
你之前见过这样的情况
And that'll do it.
首盘就此结束
Opening set, just 36 minutes
首盘只用了36分钟
for Zheng Qinwen to establish
让郑钦文确立
a quality lead
明显的优势
and foothold in this contest.
在这场比赛里站稳了脚跟
Their first ever meeting
双方首次交手
is one-way traffic.
目前完全是一边倒
All in favor of the Golden Girl.
全部有利于这位金牌姑娘
第二盘 郑钦文1比0领先
却先被对手反超
2比3之后 又连丢3局
6比2 比赛进入决胜盘
That left hand wasn't on there.
左手没有握在拍上
Nope.
没有
Oh, the forehand, exquisite.
噢 这一记正手太精妙了
It finds its way through.
这记球打穿了防守
No winners opening set,
首盘没有一个制胜分
three in the second,
第二盘已有三个
and her third produces
她的第三个制胜分
her second break of serve.
帮她第二次破发
Good effort and exposure
出色的发挥 加上曝光
at a WTA 1000 event
在WTA1000赛的舞台上
has put Alina Charaeva
让阿丽娜 恰拉耶娃
in the spotlight.
进入了大家的视野
One thing that has become
有一点已经
glaringly obvious:
再明显不过
she's a fighter.
她是个斗士
Third set coming up from Beijing.
北京站这场比赛将进入决胜盘
Five return winners in this contest
本场5个接发制胜分
for Zheng Qinwen.
都来自郑钦文
This might be the most important
这可能是最重要的
of them all.
在这五个球之中
决胜盘2比1 前3个机会被对手救下
第四次
郑钦文用反手回球直接拿下这一分
3比1 优势又回到她手里
决胜盘 郑钦文5比2领先
5比3 发球胜赛局却被破掉
5比4
她在接发局继续争取最后一分
Tomorrow she'll turn 24 years of age.
明天她就满24岁了
As Zheng Qinwen wraps up a well-earned
郑钦文为自己赢得了一份
early birthday present in Beijing.
来自北京的提前生日礼物
The tussle is over.
这场拉锯战终于结束了
And what a tussle it ended up being.
最终还真是一场苦战
Ladies and gentlemen,
女士们 先生们
Dominating the opening set,
首盘占尽优势
but had to gut out a win
最终却得苦战才赢下来
in two hours and 11 minutes.
比赛用了2小时11分钟
And Zheng Qinwen, for the second time
郑钦文第二次
in four appearances,
在4次北京站之旅中
is a quarterfinalist in Beijing.
闯进八强
39记制胜分 对手6记
进攻有威力 波动也不少
最后一局 她用回应握住胜利
生日礼物 提前到手
郑钦文已经闯进中网八强
下一场 她能继续进攻
继续耐心争每一分吗？